-这不是笑点  -我也没真笑
- That was not a joke. - That was not a real laugh.
希望你别介意我带了韦恩来
I hope you don't mind I brought Wayne along.
-韦恩是哪根葱  -正是在下
- Who's Wayne? - I'm Wayne.
我想确保他为我的嗡食网封面头条
I just wanted to make sure he had everything he needs
充分取材
for the big BuzzFeed cover story.
嗡食网是个网站  哪来的封面
BuzzFeed is a website. There is no cover.
一回事嘛  "狗狗虎虎"啦
Eh, "Tomato," "Tomato."
是"马马虎虎"好吗
It's "Tomato," "To-mah-to."
你说"马马虎虎"
You say, "Tomato," "To-mah-to,"
我说"狗狗虎虎"不行吗
I say, "Tomato," "Tomato."
戴安  我有东西给你
Oh, hey, Diane, I got you something.
机票吗
Oh, plane tickets?
是的  去旧金山的机票
Yep, to San Francisco.
阿勃丝的展览下一站就在那里
That's where the Arbus exhibit is heading next.
天呐  爱死你了  花生酱先生
Oh, my God. Thanks, Mr. Peanutbutter.